SUMMARY

I am a **PhD** candidate at **Mila**, Université de Montréal. My current research focuses on how to go from state-of-the-art large language models to AGI. In the past I've worked on NLP, Vision, Scaling Laws and Quantization, all in the context of deep learning.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Huawei

Jan. 2019 - Dec. 2019

Associate Researcher

Montreal, Canada

Compressed state-of-the-art neural machine translation models while maintaining translation quality.

Zerospam

May 2017 – Aug. 2017 / May 2018 – Aug. 2018

Research Scientist Intern

Montreal, Canada

- Developed recurrent neural networks for email spam filtering.
- Improved detection accuracy upon previously used methods.

RESEARCH

PatchBlender: A Motion Prior for Video Transformers

Oct. 2022

NeurIPS Workshop: Vision Transformers: Theory and Applications

Introduced PatchBlender, a learnable blending function that operates over patch embeddings across the temporal dimension of the latent space of Vision Transformers.

Scaling Laws for the Few-Shot Adaptation of Pre-trained Image Classifiers

Oct. 2021

ICML Workshop: Uncertainty & Robustness in Deep Learning

Showed that the few-shot generalization performance of image classifiers is well approximated by power laws as the pre-training set size increases.

Fully Quantized Transformer for Improved Translation

Sept. 2019

NeurIPS Workshop: EMC2 - Energy Efficient Training and Inference of Transformer Based Models

Fully quantized the Transformer to 8-bit while maintaining the translation quality compared to the full precision model.

Towards Lossless Encoding of Sentences

June 2019

ACL (Association for Computational Linguistics)

Proposed a near lossless method for encoding long sequences of texts into feature rich representations.

EDUCATION

Universite de Montreal

PhD, Computer Science

Sept. 2019 - Present

Montreal, Canada

GPA: 4.15/4.3, Supervisor: Alain Tapp, Sarath Chandar

Universite de Montreal

Jan. 2017 – Aug. 2019

Master's Degree, Computer Science

Montreal, Canada

GPA: 3.825/4.3, Supervisor: Alain Tapp

Universite de Montreal

Bachelor's Degree, Computer Science

Excellence Scholarship

• GPA: 3.311/4.3

Sept. 2014 — Dec. 2016 Montreal, Canada

SKILLS

• Computer: **PyTorch**, **Python**, **Numpy**, C++, C, C#, Java, Javascript, SQL, PHP

• Languages: Fluent in **English** and **French**. Basic Italian.

INTERESTS

Calisthenics, rock climbing, dancing, tabletop RPGs and board games.